Guide to the Alexander Haight family collection, 1764-1977
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 2: Legal and Financial Documents, 1813; 1852-1918; (1 box)
  This series contains personal legal and financial records of the Haight family, including deeds, receipts, contracts, and documents from the Fairfax County Court House. Specific items include court orders from 1852-1853 appointing Alexander Haight as "surveyor of the county road"; an 1864 letter from Virginia District Judge John C. Underwood on a forthcoming war-time property-confiscation trial of Alexander Haight; bank receipts of Elizabeth Haight from 1914-1919; deeds of gift from George Haight, 1895-1903; correspondence from March of 1884 regarding damage claims by Phebe Haight from the West and Sisson railroad company for damaged packages of butter; and a financial accounting record of farm land sold to Samuel Titus and Nehemiah Sweet, dated January 16, 1843.
  - Haight, Alexander: Letter from Virginia District Judge John C. Underwood to Col. Devereux, February 13, 1864 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Alexandria, Virginia; regarding property-confiscation trial of Alexander Haight
  - Haight, Alexander: Orders from Fairfax County Court, August 19, 1852; October 18, 1853 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    2 court orders appointing Alexander Haight as "surveyor of the county road"
  - Haight, Alexander: Receipts and Notes Payable, 1858-1876 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Sheriff of Fairfax, 1858; 1.
      receipt
    - For 25 bushels of corn to J. B. Gaddesss and others, September 1, 1862; 2.
    - Levy on land and personal property to Robert H. Mateer, 1872; 3.
    - L. T. Shear or Mr. Taylor, November 16, 1876; 4.
      note to pay
  - Haight, Alexander Levi: Draft classification card and check (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Draft classification card, World War I, October 31, 1918; 1.
    - National Bank of Fairfax check for $135 from Alexander Haight to Dr. S. B. Moore, January 10, 1925; 2.
  - Haight, Elizabeth: Bank receipts, 1914-1919 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    contains around 100 bank receipts and a list of credits
  - Haight, George: Deeds and certificate, 1895-1911 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Deed, February 19, 1895; 1.
    - Deed, March 6, 1899; 2.
    - Deed of Release, April 15, 1902; 3.
    - Deed of Trust, April 15, 1902; 4.
    - Deed of Release, July 15, 1903; 5.
    - Herdon Lodge No. 84, July 13, 1911; 6.
    - Envelope, October 26 [no year]; 7.
  - Haight, George: Receipts and bank check, 1888-1921 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Mosse and son, July 6, 1888; 1.
    - F. W. Richardson, September 1, 1888; 2.
    - Post office registry receipt, January 3, 1894; 3.
    - Elizabeth Sweet, October 15, 1894; 4.
    - W. E. Graham, Court Clerk, October 30, 1894; 5.
    - Post office registry receipt, January 12, 1895; 6.
    - G. M. Garrett, March 1, 1895; 7.
    - Thomas Moore, June 19, 1895; 8.
    - Margaret A. Lee, March 6, 1899; 9.
    - H. C. Haight, April 28, 1902; 10.
    - F. W. Richardson, Clerk, June 21, 1902; 11.
    - Allison Butts, October 24, 1902; 12.
    - R. E. Thorton, June 12, 1903; 13.
    - J. R. M. G., June 19, 1903; 14.
    - Walter T. Oliver, November 16, 1903; 15.
    - Ino Miller, March 6, 1899; 16.
    - H. C. Haight, April 2, 1904; 17.
    - F. W. Richardson, April 6, 1904; 18.
    - Charles E. Knight, Mutual Life Insurance Company, November 14, 1905; 19.
    - Arthur Burgess, Treasury Department, 1913; 20.
      check for 1 cent and envelope
    - H. C. Wooton, Mutual Life Insurance Company, December 1, 1913; 21.
    - National Bank of Herndon, September 1, 1916; 22.
    - National Bank of Herndon, October 21, 1916; 23.
    - E. G. Burritt, Mutual Fire Insurance Company, December, 1917; 24.
    - National Bank of Fairfax, August 11, 1920; 25.
    - R. E. Thornton, Attorney, June 13, 1921; 26.
    - R. E. Thorton, Attorney, July 11, 1921; 27.
    - F. W. Richardson, Attorney, October 24, 1921; 28.
    - Yates, undated; 29.
    - F. W. Richardson, undated; 30.
  - Haight, Helen: Insurance Title, Penn Mutual Life Insurance Company, January 22, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    2 pages
  - Haight, Henry: Deed and receipt, 1881-1884 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Phebe Haight, December 1881; 1.
      promise to pay
    - Deed, February 18, 1884; 2.
  - Haight, Phebe: Account book, 1875-1884 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Haight, Phebe: Agreement letter, March 15, 1881 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Haight, Phebe: Damage claims correspondence, March 1884 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Adams Express Company to G. W. Moss, Esq., March 8, 1884; 1.
    - Adams Express Company to G. W. Moss, Esq., March 13, 1884; 2.
    - G. W. Moss to Capt. Lucas, March 13, 1884; 3.
    - Lucas to G. W. Moss; G. W. Moss to Lucas, March 14, 1884; 4.
      two letters on one paper
    - Lucas to G. W. Moss, March 15, 1884; 5.
    - John Clayton to G. W. Moss; G. W. Moss to C. R. Bitzer, March 17, 1884; 6.
    - C. R. Bitzer to G. W. Moss, Esq.; G. W. Moss to C. R. Bitzer, March 18, 1884; March 25, 1884; 7.
    - From West and Sisson, March 24, 1884; 8.
  - Haight, Phebe: Receipts and financial statements, 1853; 1881-1898 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Witmers and Company, October 17, 1853; 1.
    - Stephen and Henry Haight, February 2, 1881; 2.
    - Thomas W. Lee, June 2, 1881; 3.
    - Riggs and Company, November 5, 1881; 4.
    - W. M. Millan, April 1882; 5.
    - J. Cooper, 1882; 6.
    - Fairfax Cemetery Association, 1882-1884; 7.
    - J. C. Fearson's Sons, January 8, 1883; 8.
    - Herbert Bryant, Dr., February 7, 1883; 9.
      monthly statement
    - James F. Carlin and Sons, March 5, 1883; 10.
    - W. E. Roby, April 16, 1883; 11.
    - G. W. M. Ramsay, Grocer, July 2, 1883; 12.
    - Phebe Haight to Mr. Bitzer, March 6, 1884; 13.
      bill
    - J. F. Oliver, September 9, 1884; 14.
    - George H. Pratt, September 24, 1884; 15.
    - J. C. Fearson's Sons, November 4, 1884; 16.
    - J. T. and J. G. Beckham, December 31, 1884; 17.
    - C. F. Wilkins and Company, January 24, 1885; 18.
    - J. T. and J. G. Beckham, October 13, 1885; 19.
    - Post office registry return receipt, November 2, 1885; 20.
    - Albert Wrenn, November 14, 1885; 21.
    - C. F. Wilkins and Company, February 6, 1886; 22.
    - E. J. Miller, Son and Company, Importers of China, Glass and Queensware, June 10, 1886; 23.
    - Jason F. Muir, Furniture Manufacturer, June 10, 1886; 24.
    - W. S. Moses and Son, June 11, 1886; 25.
    - G. W. M. Ramsay, Grocer, June 11, 1886; 26.
    - George Ryneal, Jr., June 11, 1886; 27.
    - George Watts and Son, June 11, 1886; 28.
    - J. F. Spelshouse, Agent, June 22, 1886; 29.
    - Stephen Haight, November 1886 - June 1887; 30.
    - Post office registry return receipt, February, 1888; 31.
    - Richardson, September 11, 1888; 32.
    - R. W. Moore, March 14, 1889; 33.
    - Virginia Agricultural and Mechanical College, July 25, 1889 and January 3, 1891; 34.
      two receipts
    - Post office registry return receipt, July 31, 1889; 35.
    - George Haight, November 1, 1892; 36.
    - Post office registry receipt, June 27, 1893; 37.
    - Fairfax Cemetery Association, September 19, 1894; 38.
    - Judicial statement on foreclosure of Sweet residence in Dutchess County, New York, April 30, 1898; 39.
    - J. M. Ham, May 11, 1898; 40.
    - Calling cards of Mrs. Alexander Haight and envelope, undated; 41.
      Two calling cards; one unpostmarked envelope addressed to George A. Clark and Brother
  - Haight, Samuel Dickenson and Andrew Wilson: Court summons, May 1813 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Harnesberger, Reverend A. L.: Receipts and financial statements, 1892-1905 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Johnson Harvester Company, April 15 and April 29, 1892; 1.
      receipt and letter; includes envelope
    - Firebaugh Farm, June 22 and June 23, 1904; 2.
      three receipts
    - Rockingham National Bank of Harrisonburg, June 23, July 1 and August 23, 1904; 3.
    - E. W. Carpenter, Treasurer of Rockingham County, April 1, 1905; 4.
      three receipts; includes envelope
  - Miscellaneous receipts and financial documents, 1886-1918 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Post office registry return receipt, H. C. Haight to Mr. A. B. Holtzelaw, June 14, 1886; 1.
    - F. P. May and Co. Hardware for Mrs Holtzlander, 1886; 2.
    - Mutual Fire Insurance Company of Loudoun County, 1915; 3.
    - Franklin and Co., Opticians, for Mrs. [Emma Jane] Haight, May 11, 1918; 4.
      includes a letter on the back, signed "Mother"
  - Produce books, 1897-1900 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Produce Book, September 18, 1897 - September 26, 1898; 1.
      contains records of sales and profits on produce (possibly grown on Sulley Plantation)
    - Produce Book, October 3, 1898 - April 2, 1900; 2.
  - Sweet family: Financial statement, 1842-1843 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    One-page record of mortgage and interest on 215 acres of farmland owed by Margaret Sweet and her children, including Phebe Sweet
  - Tax Receipts: Haight family, 1881-1895 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Alexander Haight, 1881-1888; 1.
      contains 6 official tax receipts and 1 hand-written note on delinquent taxes
    - George Haight, 1888-1905; 2.
      contains 23 official tax receipts and 3 hand-written notes on tax payments
    - Phebe Haight, 1881-1893; 3.
      contains 10 official tax receipts and 2 hand-written notes on tax payments
    - Stephen S. Haight, 1885-1887; 4.
      contains 2 tax receipts
- Series 3: Photographs, ca. 1863-1920; (1 box)
  This series contains around twenty original photographs and reproductions belonging to the Haight family. Subjects include Alexander, Phebe, Elizabeth, George, and Helen Haight; Fairfax County Court House; Sully Plantation; Fairfax Station during the Civil War; Alexander Haight's prize horse; and Clio, a slave girl whom Phebe Haight kept at the Sully Plantation until 1862.
  - Brady, Matthew: Civil War photograph, 1862 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    No. 427 of Brady's album gallery, titled "Prof. Lowe reconnoitering at Battle of Fair Oaks"
  - Clio, a Sulley Plantation slave, ca 1865 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    tintype of Clio, a slave girl kept by Phebe Haight from 1852 to 1862
  - Deguerrotypes, unidentified (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Two deguerrotype portraits in cases, both of the same man; in the second he is wearing a Union uniform
  - Fairfax Court House, June 1863 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    2 photographic reproductions; photographs taken by Timothy O'Sullivan
  - Fairfax Station during the Civil War, ca 1961-1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Photographic reproduction
  - Haight, Alexander and Phebe: Photographic reproductions (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Alexander Haight, 1.
      reproduced from original daguerrotype
    - Phebe Haight, 2.
  - Haight, Alexander: Prize horse (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Tintype of Alexander Haight's prize horse, 1.
    - Newsclipping facsimile explaining the story behind Haight's prize horse, 2.
    - Document granting Alexander Haight ownership of the horse, July 4, 1862; 1.
  - Miscellaneous buildings (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Old mill at Sperryville, Virginia, September 16, 1905; 1.
      photograph mounted to cardboard backing
    - The Capitol Building in Washington, DC, undated; 2.
    - Fairfax Court House, 1900; 3.
      photograph mounted on cardboard backing
    - Fairfax Court House, 1905; 4.
      photographic reproduction
    - Little Sully: Home of Alexander and Phebe Haight, undated; 3.
      photograph mounted on cardboard backing; Little Sully, Alexander and Phebe Haight's house on Sully Plantation, was built around 1851
    - Sully Daybook, 1880-1884; 4.
      thin booklet, mostly empty, with produce sales recorded on two pages
  - Miscellaneous people (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Helen Haight in nurse's uniform, undated; 1.
    - Helen Haight portrait, undated; 2.
      mounted to inside of booklet
    - Woman holding hat, undated; 3.
      subject unknown; measures 2.5" x 4.5"
    - Woman sitting at desk, 1905; 4.
      subject unknown; appears to be a photographic reproduction; measures 8" x 10"
    - Three women and a man seated outside, Spring 1889; 5.
      mounted on cardboard backing; subjects thought to be Phebe Haight, her sister Elizabeth, and Elizabeth's husband George
    - George Curry, ca. 1905; 6.
      pictured outside house with horse; measures 4.5" x 2.5"
    - George Curry, ca. 1905; 7.
      photographic reproduction of above listed photograph; measures 10" x 8"
  - Mosby and other Confederate veterans at the reunion of the Battle of Manassas, July 20, 1914 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    2 photographic reproductions and three negatives of the same photo; pictured left to right are Fountain Beattie, Lycurgus Hutcheson, John S. Mosby, and George Turbeville IV
- Series 4: Civil War Documents, ca. 1861-1865; (1 box)
  This series contains various materials pertaining to the Civil War such as civilian passes, diary excerpts, and Confederate currency. Specific items include Civil War maps and photographs; an official order from General Jackson on the day of the Battle of Chantilly (Ox Hill) prohibiting the theft or destruction of private property; documents granting passage of Alexander Haight and company into and out of Virginia; a hand-written note from the Union Major General Julius Stahel to the Union Army, attesting to the good standing of Alexander Haight; receipts of Alexander Haight for Union and Confederate supplies given out during the war; and a typed manuscript detailing the Civil War experiences of the Sutton family in Fairfax, excerpted from the diaries of Charles and Phebe Sutton.
  - Atkins Memorial, ca. 1862 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    printed statement memorializing Charles L. Atkins, a fallen Confederate soldier
  - Beauregard, General P. G. T. - Order for troops not to take forage from Sully Farm, November 25, 1861 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    signed by a Confederate officer under the command of General Beauregard
  - Civil War maps (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Sketch of 2nd Manassas, August 29th 1862, undated; 1.
    - Sketch of 2nd Manassas, August 30th 1862, undated; 2.
  - Confederate money and other Civil War and Reconstruction-era currency, 1863-1875 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Ten-dollar bill of the Confederate States of America, February 17, 1864; 1.
    - Six fifty-dollar bills of the Confederate States of America, February 17, 1864; 2.
    - Thirty one-hundred dollar bills of the Confederate States of America, February 17, 1864; 3.
    - Three-dollar bill minted by the Frontier Bank in Potsdam, New York, June 1, 1863; 4.
      features illustrations of Lady Justice, a frontier scene and a domestic scene
    - Two one-dollar bills minted by the City Bank in Augusta, Georgia, October 3, 1864; 5.
      features an illustration of a shepherd and his sheep
    - Fifty-cent bill of the United States, 1875; 6.
      front features a portrait of William Harris Crawford
  - Confederate officer's letter from Harper's Ferry, May 20, 1861 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    addressed to Father from J. L.
  - Dedication of Twin Markers: In Memorium of Major Generals Philip Kearny and Isaac Ingalls Stevens, October 2, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    pamphlet from ceremony memorializing fallen Union generals
  - Haight, Alexander: Civil War passes, 1862-1865 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Passes issued by various Provost Marshals' Offices granting Alexander Haight safe passage to and from various points in Northern Virginia
    - Pass No. 97, March 25, 1862; 1.
    - Pass, November 2, 1862; 2.
    - Pas No. 543, November 19, 1862; 3.
    - Pass, November 21, 1862; 4.
    - Pass, October 30, 1862; 5.
    - Pass, November 9, 1862; 6.
    - Pass, December 1, 1862; 7.
    - Pass, December 11, 1862; 8.
    - Pass, 1862; 9.
    - Pass No. 2232, February 25, 1863; 10.
    - Pass, June 16, 1863; 11.
    - Pass, March 13, 1864; 12.
    - Pass, October 24, 1864; 13.
    - Pass No. 1749, March 2, 1865; 14.
  - Haight, Alexander: Claim for army damages, September 17, 1862 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    claim assembled by neighbors of Alexander Haight for damages incurred when the Confederate army passed through on September 1, 1862
  - Haight, Alexander: Union officer letters affirming Haight's loyalty to the Union (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Robert Johnstone, March 7, 1863; 1.
    - Union Major General Julius Stahel, June 20, 1863; 2.
  - Haight, Alexander: Receipts for provisions for Union and Confederate Armies, 1861 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - For the use of one horse, August 24, 1861; 1.
    - For 10,000 pounds of hay, October 7, 1861; 2.
    - For 370 bushels of corn used for horse feed, November 13, 1861; 3.
  - Jackson, General T. J. "Stonewall": Order on damages, September 1, 1862 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    order of General Jackson prohibiting theft of private property, signed by Jackson's officers
  - Porter, General Fitz John: Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Gen. Fitz John Porter to Col. F. J. Parker, January 24, 1863; 1.
    - Printed letter from General Fitz John Porter to the Secretary of War, January 9, 1871; 2.
      letter regarding publication of maps of the Battle of Manassas
  - Sutton, Charles and Phebe: The Civil War Experiences of a Northern Family Settled in Virginia, ca 1861-1865 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    edited and transcribed from the diaries of Charles and Phebe Sutton by their daughter, Alice Coates
- Series 5: Publications and Serials, (1 box)
  This series contains seven illustrated monthly magazines and a book titled War Reminiscences by the Surgeon of Mosby's Command (1890). The magazines include issues of The Century, The Cosmopolitan, and McClure's.
  - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine, 1884-1885 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine, November 1884; 1.
    - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine, April 1885; 2.
  - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine, 1885 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine, August 1885; 1.
    - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine, October 1885; 2.
  - The Century Illustrated Monthly Magazine, January 1890 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - The Cosmopolitan: An Illustrated Monthly Magazine, March 1898 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - McClure's Magazine, January 1900 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - War Reminiscences by the Surgeon of Mosby's Command, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Series 6: Miscellaneous, 1764-1976; (2 boxes)
  This series contains miscellaneous printed materials, notes, and facsimiles. Materials include old business cards; brochures on local history; a newspaper facsimile (ca. 1975) on old Fairfax families, the Haights and Milans; a scrap book of old newsclippings; and a ledger full of accounting records dating from before the Revolutionary War.
  - Brochures and publications on historic sites, 1907-1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - The Jamestown Exposition, Illustrated, 1907; 1.
    - Christ Church, Philadelphia, ca. 1934; 2.
    - Fairfax County Court House Rededication, 1967; 3.
      pamphlet
    - Historic Fairfax Court House, May 1967; 4.
    - Echoes History, Index, November 1970 to November 1971, 5.
      Pioneer America Society publication
    - Echoes History, Volume 1, No. 3, March 1971; 6.
      article on Little Sully; publication of the Pioneer America Society
    - The Old West, 1973; 7.
      advertisement for Time-Life encyclopedia on the Old West
    - Historical Society of Fairfax County, Virginia, Inc., Volume 14, 1976-1977; 8.
    - Church Buildings of the Diocese of New Jersey, undated; 9.
    - Views, State Normal School, Farmville, Virginia, undated; 10.
      brochure with photographic illustrations
  - Illustration, Virginia road map, and violin strings (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Illustration of woman, framed, ca. 1902; 1.
    - Rand-McNally Indexed Pocket Map and Auto Road Guide, Virginia, 1919; 2.
    - E. F. Droop and Sons, Co., Violin D String (Guitar G), undated; 3.
      string sleeve with two strings inside
  - King Solomon's Song, shorthand version, 1894 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    leather bound pocket size book
  - Notes and newsclippings, 1881-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Note: Certificate to deed, Haight to Sweet, April 15, 1881; 1.
    - Newsclipping of obituary for Henry P. Titus, 1928; 2.
    - Newspaper article facsimile: "Members of Old Fairfax Families Share Memories of Yesterday,", ca. 1976; 3.
      from the Globes Northern Virginia Bicentennial Review; discusses the history of the Haight and Millan families
    - Copy of typewritten notes from the joint meeting of the Board of Supervisors of Washington County and the County School Board of Washington County, undated; 4.
    - Letter, signed Your Dear Boy, undated; 5.
      sender and recipient both unknown
    - Note, Hon. C. Bascom Slemp, undated; 6.
    - Note on the Sweet family, undated; 7.
    - Fragment of paper with school marks, undated; 8.
    - Handwritten notes, "Old Talks at Home", undated; 9.
      4 pages
    - Handwritten picadilla recipe, undated; 10.
  - Poems (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - "Kaiser Bill,", undated; 1.
    - "The Old Dore Step,", undated; 2.
      fragment of poem written on looseleaf paper
    - "To the Memory of Ida,", undated; 3.
    - "George Washington" and "Trust", undated; 4.
  - Postcards and birthday cards (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Dare Marker, Fort Raleigh, Roanoke Island, North Carolina, undated; 1.
      2 postcards
    - Historic Bullet Scarred Tree on Bull Run Battlefield, undated; 2.
    - Reno's Famous Town House Dining Room, undated; 3.
    - Old Hicksite Quaker Church, undated; 4.
    - John Q. Marr Monument, Fairfax, Virginia, undated; 5.
    - The Tavern, Fairfax, Virginia, undated; 6.
    - A Birthday Wish, from Mother to Aleck, 1937; 7.
      birthday card
    - Birthday Wishes, from Mother to Acleck, 1938; 8.
    - Christmas card, undated; 9.
    - Cap d'Antibes, undated; 10.
      picture of the cape
  - Printed materials: Calling cards, business cards, funeral sermons, etc. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Calling cards, undated; 1.
      10 calling cards: Mr. Harry L. Cather, Mrs. Frank Page, Gamett Ford, W. W. Millan, Jr., Carrie Ballinger, Mrs. Leda Terwilliger, Ella J. Worley, Miss Frankie M. Vosburgh, May Childs Furbrow, Mrs. Alice Hamill
    - The Syracuse Land and Improvement Company, undated; 2.
      business card
    - Edward P. Mertz Wholesale and Retail Druggist, undated; 3.
      business card/tag
    - Pennsylvania Railroad Company ticket for the Jersey City Ferry, undated; 4.
    - Declaration of Independence and Washington's Farewell Address, December 1, 1896; 5.
      Young Folk's Library of Choice Literature, Vol. III, No. 66
    - "Principal Cities of the United States,", undated; 6.
      old guide book with illustrations
    - Goodwill Commandery of the United Order of the Golden Cross (UOGC), 1832; 7.
      concert program for the UOGC, a Christian voluntary association
    - Brief notes of the sermon for funeral of Mrs. Susie Barnes Allen, 1884; 8.
    - Eye-Glasses of Mr. Isaac Alexander, undated; 9.
      advertisement circular boasting "The only Eye-Glasses for which was awarded Medal and Diploma at the Centennial Exhibition of 1876."
    - Chr. Hansen's Danish Butter Coloring, undated; 10.
      advertisement circular boasting product as winner of "the Prize Medal at Philadelphia, 1876 and three gold medals at Paris, 1878."
    - Henry McShane and Co. Church Bells, undated; 11.
      advertisement circular
    - Draft registration notification envelope, 1940; 12.
      bears United States seal and photograph of Franklin D. Roosevelt
    - Virginia License to Operate a Motor Vehicle, November 23, 1941; 13.
      issued by the United States Department of the Interior National Park Service
    - Aetna Insurance Company, 14.
      envelope
  - Ledger and scrapbook, ca. 1838-1900 (Box 7)
    ledger consists of only a few pages; scrapbook contains newsclippings pertaining to the Civil War
  - Ledger, 1764-1808 (Box 8)
    full leather-bound account book from a trading post on Lake George
- Series 7: Oversize, 1863-1966; (1 box)